Guide to the The New Leader Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Artwork, 1928-2006, undated
  - Subseries V. 4: Artwork and Covers--Oversized--by Artist, 1961-1998, undated
    - Weston, Armand
      - Covers
        - Untitled, 5 August 1963 (Box 166, Folder 22)
        - Untitled, 19 June 1967 (Box 166, Folder 23)
        - Untitled, 1 September/25 August 1969 (Box 166, Folder 24)
    - Wilmoth, Grant E.--Untitled--Cover, 1998 (Box 166, Folder 25)
    - [Zimgaulli, J.]--Untitled--Cover, 15 March 1976 (Box 166, Folder 26)
  - Subseries V. 5: Mechanicals--Oversized, 1961-1994
    Subseries 5 contains mechanicals for advertisements, promotional materials, and magazine layouts, as well as several posters. Organized by type and size, the designer is also noted if known.
    - Books Issue
      - 1976-1988 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Michael Aron and Co., 1987-1994, undated, (3 Folders) (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Books Issue (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - Lubalin Peckolick Associates, 1981 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Peckolick and Partners, 1987 (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - The Pushpin Group, 1986 (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Pushpin Lubalin Peckolick, 1982-1985, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 169, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Tana and Co., 1988 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Design Mockups, 1961-1999, undated (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Poster
      - Eugene Lyons Column, undated (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - The New Leader Anniversary, undated (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Promotional Mechanicals
      - Undated (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - Gerson Offset Lithography Co., Inc., 1970-1972, (3 Folders) (Box 170, Folder 5 to 7)
      - Herb Lubalin, undated (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Special Issues, 1963-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 171, Folder 1 to 2)
    - General
      - Ad Plate--New York Times Back Page, March 5, 1968 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Poster
        - Herb Lubalin, 1966, (3 Folders) (Box 172, Folder 2 to 4)
        - The New Leader 14th Anniversary, 1936 (Box 172, Folder 5)
        - The New Leader, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 172, Folder 6 to 7)
      - Promotional Mechanicals and Copy
        - Undated (Box 172, Folder 8)
        - Herb Lubalin Inc., 1968, (3 Folders) (Box 172, Folder 9 to 11)
        - William Steiner Associates, Inc., undated, (2 Folders) (Box 172, Folder 12 to 13)
  - Subseries 6: New York Public Library Exhibit--Oversized, 1957-1973
    Subseries 6 contains artwork selected for an exhibit of The New Leader’s art at the New York Public Library. The pieces are organized by artist, by date within artist, and by size. Some pieces were selected for the exhibit and not used; pieces not used are noted as such in the folder title.
    - DeVoto, Joe--untitled, undated (not used) (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Fernandez, Julio
      - J. William Fulbright and Everett Dirksen, 23 October 1967 (not used) (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Artur Costa E Silva, 20 June 1969 (not used) (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - Geller, Barry
      - Nikita Khrushchev and Mao Tse Tung, 19 March 1962 (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - Untitled, 14 September 1964 (not used) (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - Kosygin and Brezhnev, 25 April 1966 (not used) (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - Untitled, undated, (4 Folders) (Box 173, Folder 8 to 11)
    - [Gersten, Gerry]--Marshal Tito, 1962-1970 (not used) (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Gersten, Gerry
      - Leonid Brezhnev, 19 March 1973 (not used) (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - Untitled, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 173, Folder 14)
      - Untitled, undated (not used) (Box 173, Folder Md)
    - Kearns, J.
      - Untitled--Cover, undated (Box 173, Folder md)
    - Thompson, Mozelle--untitled, undated (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified--undated (not used) (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified--undated (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Bendis, Keith--Untitled, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 174, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Berg Victor, Joan--Untitled, undated (not used) (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Berry, William
      - Correspondence--Kyriakides, Stanley--Cyprus’ Green Line, 1967, undated (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - The Green Line in Nicosia--Barrels Divide the Street, undated (not used) (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Greek Coffee Shop in Nicosia, undated (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - [Eutemey]--Untitled, undated (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Fernandez, Julio
      - Golda Meir, 31 March 1969 (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Untitled, undated (not used) (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Geller, Barry
      - Barry Goldwater, 18 September 1961 (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - Fidel Castro, 16 April 1962 (Box 174, Folder 11)
      - Milovan Djilas, 9 July 1962 (Box 174, Folder 12)
      - Charles de Gaulle, 4 March 1963 (not used) (Box 174, Folder 13)
      - Martin Luther King Jr., June 1963 (Box 174, Folder 14)
      - Joe Valachi, 23 December 1963 (Box 174, Folder 15)
      - Charles de Gaulle et Mao Tse Tung, 17 February 1964 (Box 174, Folder 16)
      - Untitled, 15 February 1965 (Box 174, Folder 17)
      - Juan Bosch, 24 May 1965 (not used) (Box 174, Folder 18)
      - Albania, 13 September 1965 (Box 174, Folder 19)
      - Untitled, 14 August 1967 (not used) (Box 174, Folder 20)
      - Creighton Abrams, 9 June 1969 (Box 174, Folder 21)
      - Untitled, 21 February 1972 (Box 174, Folder 22)
      - Ellsworth Bunker, undated (Box 174, Folder 23)
      - Nkrumah, undated (Box 174, Folder 24)
      - Untitled, undated (not used) (Box 174, Folder 25)
    - Gersten, Gerry
      - Macmillan, 30 October 1961 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Untitled, 1961-1963 (not used) (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - V.K. Krisha Menon, 1961-1967 (not used) (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - Untitled, 1962-1967 (not used) (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Untitled, 27 December 1971 (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 2 April 1973 (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Norman Mailer, 17 September 1973 (Box 175, Folder 7)
      - Richard Nixon, 12 November 1973 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Henry Kissinger, Undated (Box 175, Folder 9)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Kweskin, Sam
      - Aybib Khan, 2 March 1964 (Box 175, Folder 11)
      - Ludwig Erhard, Nasser and Walter Ulbricht, 1 March 1965 (not used) (Box 175, Folder 12)
      - Untitled, 2 February 1973 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - Marshall, F.--Untitled, 1972 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - [Marshall, F.]--Untitled, undated (not used) (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Stevens, Elisabeth--Untitled, undated (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - [Stevens,]--Artist’s Proof, 1957 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - Myers, Lou--Untitled, undated (not used) (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - M.P., Touré, 15 October 1962 (not used) (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - Unidentified--Adolf Hitler and Nikita Khrushchev, 2 October 1961, undated (not used) (Box 175, Folder 20)
    - Unidentified
      - 9 July 1962 (Box 175, Folder 21)
      - 30 September 1963 (Box 175, Folder 22)
      - Wang Hung Wen, Yao Wen Yuan, Chung Chun Chiao, Chiang Ching, Undated (not used) (Box 175, Folder 23)
      - Undated, (3 Folders) (Box 175, Folder 24 to 26)
    - Weston, Armand, Vatican, 1964 (not used) (Box 175, Folder 27)
- Series VI: Photographs, 1906-2005, undated
  The photographs in this series are primarily black and white and are sourced from newswire services such as Wide World Photos, which provided a caption with a date and brief description of the photograph. They are sorted alphabetically by subject. The subjects include countries and cities; individuals, including politicians, world leaders, and cultural figures; events, including world conferences, wars, and protests; and miscellaneous subjects, such as airports, basketball, parks, and atomic bombs. The photographs represent both domestic and international scenes, and there is particular emphasis on individuals, places and subjects related to the Soviet Union, Socialism, and Communism, such as the Solidarity movement in Poland and scenes in East and West Berlin. Some folder titles, such as “U.S. Underworlds, Gangsters,” “Wetbacks,” and “Wild West,” defy easy categorization. The last two boxes contain stock publicity photos of writers, dancers, musicians, and actors.
  - Subseries 1: Photographs by Subject, 1924-2005, undated
    Subseries 1 includes the bulk of the photographs obtained from newswire services, organized alphabetically by subject.
  - Abbas, Ferhat--Algeria, 1958-1960 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Abdullah of Jordan 1951, undated (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Abdullah of Kashmir, 1948-1949 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Abel, I.W., 1964-1965 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Abrams, Charles, undated (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Abrams, Creighton, 1966-1968 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Abt, Wohn, 1948 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Acheson, Dean, 1951, undated (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Ackley, Gardner, 1962-1968 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - ADA groups, 1950 (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Adams, Brock, 1977-1979 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Adams, Paul L., 1966 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - Adams, Sherman, 1958-undated (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Adenauer, Konrad--German chancellor, 1945-1957, undated (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - AFL-CIO Merger, 1955 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - Afghanistan Scenes, 1972-2001 (Box 176, Folder 16)
  - Addonizio, Hugh--Mayor of Newark, 1965-1966 (Box 176, Folder 17)
  - Africa--Scenes, 1947-1984, undated (Box 176, Folder 18)
  - Aganbegyan, Abel, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 19)
  - Agnew, Spiro T., 1966-1968 (Box 176, Folder 20)
  - Agriculture, undated (Box 176, Folder 21)
  - Aidit, D.N., 1965 (Box 176, Folder 22)
  - Aiken, George W., 1949, undated (Box 176, Folder 23)
  - Airports/Airlines/Airplanes, 1991, undated (Box 176, Folder 24)
  - Akram, Munir, 2003 (Box 176, Folder 25)
  - Albania, 1953-1961, undated (Box 176, Folder 26)
  - Albert, Carl, 1966-1974 (Box 176, Folder 27)
  - Albosta, Donald, 1983 (Box 176, Folder 28)
  - Albred, James, 1937 (Box 176, Folder 29)
  - Albright, Madeleine K., 1993-1998 (Box 176, Folder 30)
  - Aldouri, Mohammed A., 2003 (Box 176, Folder 31)
  - Aleman, Miguel, 1947, undated (Box 176, Folder 32)
  - Alessandri, Arturo, undated (Box 176, Folder 33)
  - Alessandri, George, 1959-1963, undated (Box 176, Folder 34)
  - Alexander, Archibald, 1952 (Box 176, Folder 35)
  - Alexandrov, Georgy Fedorovich, 1955 (Box 176, Folder 36)
  - Alexander, Earl, 1952 (Box 176, Folder 37)
  - Algeria, 1942-1965, undated (Box 176, Folder 38)
  - Alfonsin, Raul, undated (Box 176, Folder 39)
  - Alford, Dale, 1959, undated (Box 176, Folder 40)
  - Alger, Fred, undated (Box 176, Folder 41)
  - Al-Hussein, Prince Al Amir Zeid Ib, 1958 (Box 176, Folder 42)
  - Alioto, Joseph, 1969-1974 (Box 176, Folder 43)
  - Alkimin, Jose Maria, 1964 (Box 176, Folder 44)
  - Allen, George U., 1948, undated (Box 176, Folder 45)
  - Allen, Ivan, Jr., 1961-1962 (Box 176, Folder 46)
  - Allen, Richard, 1980-1981 (Box 176, Folder 47)
  - Allende, Dr. Salvador, 1961-1970, undated (Box 176, Folder 48)
  - Allon, Yigol, 1968-1969, undated (Box 176, Folder 49)
  - Almirante, Giorgio, 1972 (Box 176, Folder 50)
  - Almond, Gov. J. Lindsay, 1958-1959 (Box 176, Folder 51)
  - Alsography, undated (Box 176, Folder 52)
  - Alvarez, Alberto, 1949 (Box 176, Folder 53)
  - Ambedkar, Dr. B.R., undated (Box 176, Folder 54)
  - Amin, Idi, 1975-1977 (Box 176, Folder 55)
  - Amital, Yuhuda, undated (Box 176, Folder 56)
  - Amte, Baba, undated (Box 176, Folder 57)
  - Anastasia, Anthony, 1955 (Box 176, Folder 58)
  - Anderson, Clinton P., 1954-1957 (Box 176, Folder 59)
  - Anderson, John, 1979-1980, undated (Box 176, Folder 60)
  - Anderson, Robert B., 1954, undated (Box 176, Folder 61)
  - Anderson, Wendell, undated (Box 176, Folder 62)
  - Amer, Field Marshal, 1966 (Box 176, Folder 63)
  - Amalrik, Andrei, 1971 (Box 176, Folder 64)
  - Andreotti, Giulio, 1978, undated (Box 176, Folder 65)
  - Andrews, Gen. James, 1959 (Box 176, Folder 66)
  - Andropov, Yuri Vladimirovich, 1971-1983, undated (Box 176, Folder 67)
  - Andrus, Cecil, 1977 (Box 176, Folder 68)
  - Anendola, Giorgia, 1969 (Box 176, Folder 69)
  - Angell, Sir Norman, undated (Box 176, Folder 70)
  - Angola, 1961-1976 (Box 176, Folder 71)
  - Annan, Kofi, 1996-2003, undated (Box 176, Folder 72)
  - Anslinger, Harry, 1952 (Box 176, Folder 73)
  - Antonini, Luigi, undated (Box 176, Folder 74)
  - Aptheker, Herbert, undated (Box 176, Folder 75)
  - Arafat, Yasir, 1969-1995, undated (Box 176, Folder 76)
  - Aranne, Zalmen, 1958 (Box 176, Folder 77)
  - Archer, W.P., 1977 (Box 176, Folder 78)
  - Arciniegas, German, undated (Box 176, Folder 79)
  - Arens, Moshe, 1983, undated (Box 176, Folder 80)
  - Arevelo, Jose, undated (Box 176, Folder 81)
  - Argentina--Scenes, 1946-1983, undated (Box 176, Folder 82)
  - Aridor, Yoram, 1981 (Box 176, Folder 83)
  - Aristide, Jean-Bertrand, 1988, 1993 (Box 176, Folder 84)
  - Armstrong, Judge Geo.--Fascist millionaire, undated (Box 176, Folder 85)
  - Armstrong, William, 1980, 1983 (Box 176, Folder 86)
  - Army-McCarthy Hearing, 1954, undated (Box 176, Folder 87)
  - Army--U.S.--Scenes, 1951-1963, undated (Box 176, Folder 88)
  - Arnall, Ellis, 1952, undated (Box 176, Folder 89)
  - Arnold, Brig. Gen. Wm. H., undated (Box 176, Folder 90)
  - Arrighi, Pascal, 1958 (Box 176, Folder 91)
  - Arvey, Jacob H., undated (Box 176, Folder 92)
  - Asanuma, Inajiro, 1948 (Box 176, Folder 93)
  - Ashmore, Harry S., 1954, undated (Box 176, Folder 94)
  - Askew, Reubin, 1970-1974 (Box 176, Folder 95)
  - Aspinwall, Wayne, undated (Box 176, Folder 96)
  - Assad, Hafez El of Syria, 1967-1978 (Box 176, Folder 97)
  - Atkins, Humphrey, 1973, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 98)
  - Atom, accidents, 1978-1979 (Box 176, Folder 99)
  - Atom bomb and cannon, 1952-1957 (Box 176, Folder 100)
  - A-bomb protests, 1958-1961 (Box 176, Folder 101)
  - Atomic energy plant, undated (Box 176, Folder 102)
  - Atomic submarines, 1955-1959 (Box 176, Folder 103)
  - Atoms for Peace Conference, 1958 (Box 176, Folder 104)
  - Attassi, Noureddin, 1966-1970 (Box 176, Folder 105)
  - Attlee, Clement, 1945-1951, undated (Box 176, Folder 106)
  - Auriol, Vincent, 1958, undated (Box 176, Folder 107)
  - Austin, Warren R., 1947, 1950, undated (Box 176, Folder 108)
  - Australia--scenes, 1942-1983, undated (Box 176, Folder 109)
  - Austria, 1945-1977 (Box 176, Folder 110)
  - Austria--treaty signing, 1955-1956, undated (Box 176, Folder 111)
  - Ayub, Mohammed, 1947 (Box 176, Folder 112)
  - Babioch, Edward, 1977, undated (Box 176, Folder 113)
  - Babu, Abdul Rahman--Foreign Minister of Zanzibar, 1964 (Box 176, Folder 114)
  - Badger, Adm. Oscar C., undated (Box 176, Folder 115)
  - Badillo, Herman, 1969 (Box 176, Folder 116)
  - Bailey, John M., 1959-1970 (Box 176, Folder 117)
  - Baker, Bobby, 1963 (Box 176, Folder 118)
  - Baker, Sen. Howard, 1967-1979, undated (Box 176, Folder 119)
  - Baker, James A., III, undated (Box 176, Folder 120)
  - Bakke, Allan, 1977-1978 (Box 176, Folder 121)
  - Bakshi, Ghulan Mohammed, undated (Box 176, Folder 122)
  - Balaguer, Joaquin, 1961, undated (Box 176, Folder 123)
  - Balbin, Ricardo, 1957 (Box 176, Folder 124)
  - Baldridge, Malcolm, 1983 (Box 176, Folder 125)
  - Baldwin, Roger, 1938-1949 (Box 176, Folder 126)
  - Ball, George, 1964-1968 (Box 176, Folder 127)
  - Balkan Pact, 1954, undated (Box 176, Folder 128)
  - Banda, Dr. Hastings, 1959-1964 (Box 176, Folder 129)
  - Bandaranaike, S.W.R.D., 1956 (Box 176, Folder 130)
  - Bandung--Asian-African conference, 1955, undated (Box 176, Folder 131)
  - Banzer, Hugo, 1971-1972 (Box 176, Folder 132)
  - Bao Dai, 1948-1952, undated (Box 176, Folder 133)
  - Barbie, Klaus, undated (Box 176, Folder 134)
  - Barco, Virgilio, 1986 (Box 176, Folder 135)
  - Baring, Sir Evelyn, 1952 (Box 176, Folder 136)
  - Barkan, Alexander, 1972, 1974 (Box 176, Folder 137)
  - Barkley, Alben W., undated (Box 176, Folder 138)
  - Barkley, Alvin, undated (Box 176, Folder 139)
  - Barmine, Alexander, 1951, undated (Box 176, Folder 140)
  - Baroody, Jamil M., 1969 (Box 176, Folder 141)
  - Barre, Raymond, undated (Box 176, Folder 142)
  - Barrera, Antonio, 1963 (Box 176, Folder 143)
  - Barrientos, Rene, 1964 (Box 176, Folder 144)
  - Barth, John, undated (Box 176, Folder 145)
  - Baruch, Bernard, 1935-1953, undated (Box 176, Folder 146)
  - Barzel, Rainer, 1965, undated (Box 176, Folder 147)
  - Baseball, 1969, undated (Box 176, Folder 148)
  - Basketball, undated (Box 176, Folder 149)
  - Batchelor, Claude, 1954 (Box 176, Folder 150)
  - Bates, Mrs. L.C., 1957 (Box 176, Folder 151)
  - Batsanov, Sergei, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 152)
  - Barista, Fulgencio, 1953-1957, undated (Box 176, Folder 153)
  - Bayar, Celal, 1950, 1960, undated (Box 176, Folder 154)
  - Bayh, Birch, undated (Box 176, Folder 155)
  - Beaches--Scenes, 1953, 1957, undated (Box 176, Folder 156)
  - Beam, Jacob, 1958 (Box 176, Folder 157)
  - Beame, Abraham, 1965-1975 (Box 176, Folder 158)
  - Beaverbrook, Lord, undated (Box 176, Folder 159)
  - Bebler, Ales, 1948 (Box 176, Folder 160)
  - Becher, Johannes R., undated (Box 176, Folder 161)
  - Beck, Dave, undated (Box 176, Folder 162)
  - Begin, Menachem/Sadat, Anwar, 1977, 1988, undated (Box 176, Folder 163)
  - Begun, Iosif, undated (Box 176, Folder 164)
  - Begin, Menachem, 1948-1980 (Box 176, Folder 165)
  - Bein, Johanan, Ambassador, undated (Box 176, Folder 166)
  - Belaunde, Fernando, 1962 (Box 176, Folder 167)
  - Belaunde, Victor A., 1953-1957 (Box 176, Folder 168)
  - Belgium, 1978 (Box 176, Folder 169)
  - Bell, Daniel, undated (Box 176, Folder 170)
  - Bell, David E., 1960 (Box 176, Folder 171)
  - Bell, Elliot V., 1956 (Box 176, Folder 172)
  - Bell, Griffin, 1976-1977 (Box 176, Folder 173)
  - Bell, Laird, undated (Box 176, Folder 174)
  - Bell, Terrel, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 175)
  - Belli, Melvin, undated (Box 176, Folder 176)
  - Beloff, Max, undated (Box 176, Folder 177)
  - Ben-Gharon, Itzhak, undated (Box 176, Folder 178)
  - Ben Barka, Ahmed, 1965 (Box 176, Folder 179)
  - Ben Bella, Ahmed, 1956-1963 (Box 176, Folder 180)
  - Benchley, Robert and Nathaniel, undated (Box 176, Folder 181)
  - Benes, Edward, undated (Box 176, Folder 182)
  - Ben-Gurion, David, 1956-1960, undated (Box 176, Folder 183)
  - Benn, A. Wedgwood, 1975-1980, undated (Box 176, Folder 184)
  - Bennett, Robert, 1964-1969 (Box 176, Folder 185)
  - Ben Salah, Ahmed, 1969 (Box 176, Folder 186)
  - Benson, Ezra Taft, 1957-1958, undated (Box 176, Folder 187)
  - Bentley, Elizabeth 1943-1951 (Box 176, Folder 188)
  - Benton, William, undated (Box 176, Folder 189)
  - Benvenuti, Ludovico, 1959 (Box 176, Folder 190)
  - Ben-Zv, Izhak, 1960 (Box 176, Folder 191)
  - Bergland, Robert, 1977 (Box 176, Folder 192)
  - Berkeley, U. of C., 1949-1977 (Box 176, Folder 193)
  - Berle, Adolf A., undated (Box 176, Folder 194)
  - [West] Berlin/Berlin Wall, 1943-1981 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Berlin, June 17, 1953 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Bernardino, Felix, 1953 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Bernstein, Eduard, undated (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Berres, Luis Battle, 1955 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Betancourt, Ernesto, undated (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Betancourt, Romulo, 1961-1963 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Bevan, Aneurin, 1950-1959, undated (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Berlinguer, Enrico, 1977-1979, undated (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Bermuda Conference, 1953 (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Bevin, Ernest, 1950, undated (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Bhave, Acharya Vinobha, undated (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - Bhindranwale, Jarnail Singh, 1984, undated (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - Bhutan, 1958-1959 (Box 177, Folder 14)
  - Bidault, Georges, 1953, undated (Box 177, Folder 15)
  - Biemiller, Andrew J., undated (Box 177, Folder 16)
  - Big 3 For. Ministers--Lancaster, 1950 (Box 177, Folder 17)
  - Big Four Foreign Ministers--New York, 1946 (Box 177, Folder 18)
  - Billingsley, Sherman, undated (Box 177, Folder 19)
  - Billotte, Pierre, 1957-1962 (Box 177, Folder 20)
  - Binh, Mrs. Nguyen Thi, 1969 (Box 177, Folder 21)
  - Birch, John, 1961 (Box 177, Folder 22)
  - Birmingham, Ala., 1963 (Box 177, Folder 23)
  - Bisson, T.A., undated (Box 177, Folder 24)
  - Bizri, Gen. Afif, 1956 (Box 177, Folder 25)
  - Black, Eugene R. 1949-1957, undated (UN-IBRD) (Box 177, Folder 26)
  - Black, Justice Hugo, 1957, undated (Box 177, Folder 27)
  - Blackmun, Harry A., 1970 (Box 177, Folder 28)
  - Blair, Tony, 1998-1999, undated (Box 177, Folder 29)
  - Blanco, Salvador Jorge, 1982 (Box 177, Folder 30)
  - Blatchford, Joseph H., 1969 (Box 177, Folder 31)
  - Bliss, Ray, 1964-1965 (Box 177, Folder 32)
  - Blix, Hans, 2003 (Box 177, Folder 33)
  - Blossom, Virgil T., 1957 (Box 177, Folder 34)
  - Blough, Roger, 1959-1962, undated (Box 177, Folder 35)
  - Blum, Leon, undated (Box 177, Folder 36)
  - Blum, Yehuda, 1982 (Box 177, Folder 37)
  - Blumenthal, Michael W., 1977-1978 (Box 177, Folder 38)
  - Boggs, Hale, 1968-1970 (Box 177, Folder 39)
  - Boggs, Lindy, 1973 (Box 177, Folder 40)
  - Bogota Riots, 1948 (Box 177, Folder 41)
  - Bohlen, Charles E., 1947-1957 (Box 177, Folder 42)
  - Bohn, William E., 1967 (Box 177, Folder 43)
  - Bierut, Bolislaw, 1947-1955 (Box 177, Folder 44)
  - Bolivia--Scenes, 1952-1965, undated (Box 177, Folder 45)
  - Bolling, Richard, undated (Box 177, Folder 46)
  - Bolton, Frances P., undated (Box 177, Folder 47)
  - Bolz, Lothar, 1959, undated (Box 177, Folder 48)
  - Bonnelly, Rafael, 1962 (Box 177, Folder 49)
  - Bonner, Yelena, 1975 (Box 177, Folder 50)
  - Bonnet, Henri, 1949 (Box 177, Folder 51)
  - Booth, Cherie, 2000 (Box 177, Folder 52)
  - Borge, Tomas, 1979, 1983, undated (Box 177, Folder 53)
  - Borges, Ignacio Iribarren, 1964 (Box 177, Folder 54)
  - Bork, Robert, undated (Box 177, Folder 55)
  - Bormann, Martin, 1960 (Box 177, Folder 56)
  - Borusewicz, Bogdan, undated (Box 177, Folder 57)
  - Bosch, Juan, 1963 (Box 177, Folder 58)
  - Bossay, Luis, undated (Box 177, Folder 59)
  - Boston--U. of, 1968 (Box 177, Folder 60)
  - Botha, Pieter, 1978-1979 (Box 177, Folder 61)
  - Botha, R.F., 1977-1978, undated (Box 177, Folder 62)
  - Boulloche, Andre, 1959 (Box 177, Folder 63)
  - Boumedienne, 1962-1970 (Box 177, Folder 64)
  - Boumendjel, Ahmed, 1958, 1960 (Box 177, Folder 65)
  - Bourges-Manoury, Maruice, 1957, undated (Box 177, Folder 66)
  - Bourghiba, 1952-1973, undated (Box 177, Folder 67)
  - Boutros-Ghali, Boutros, 1990-1994 (Box 177, Folder 68)
  - Bowles, Bryant, undated (Box 177, Folder 69)
  - Bowles, Chester, 1951-1960 (Box 177, Folder 70)
  - Bowring, Sen. Eva, 1954 (Box 177, Folder 71)
  - Boyle, William S., undated (Box 177, Folder 72)
  - Bradley, Omar, undated (Box 177, Folder 73)
  - Bradley, Ralph, undated (Box 177, Folder 74)
  - Bradley, Capt. William, 1955(Lila) (Box 177, Folder 75)
  - Brady, James S., 1981 (Box 177, Folder 76)
  - Branco, Castello, 1964 (Box 177, Folder 77)
  - Brandt, Willy, 1959-1976 (Box 177, Folder 78)
  - Brannan, Charles, 1950-1956, undated (Box 177, Folder 79)
  - Bratkowski, Stefan, undated (Box 177, Folder 80)
  - Brauer, Max, undated (Box 177, Folder 81)
  - Brazil--Scenes, 1928-1984 (Box 177, Folder 82)
  - Breathitt, Edward, 1961 (Box 177, Folder 83)
  - Brecht, Bert, 1947 (Box 177, Folder 84)
  - Breech, Ernest R., 1954 (Box 177, Folder 85)
  - Brennan, Justice William J., 1956-1965 (Box 177, Folder 86)
  - Bretano, Heinrich Von, 1959 (Box 177, Folder 87)
  - Bretcher, W., undated (Box 177, Folder 88)
  - Brewster, Kingman, 1963-1977 (Box 177, Folder 89)
  - Brezhnev, Leonid, 1961-1979 (Box 177, Folder 90)
  - Brian, Aristide, undated (Box 177, Folder 91)
  - Bricker, Sen. John W., undated (Box 177, Folder 92)
  - Bridges, Styles, 1952, undated (Box 177, Folder 93)
  - Brik, Lili, 1914 (Box 177, Folder 94)
  - Britain -- atomic plants, 1954-1982 (Box 177, Folder 95)
  - Britain--Royal Family, 1951-1956, undated (Box 177, Folder 96)
  - Britain--Scenes, 1939-1974, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 177, Folder 97 to 98)
  - Britain--Demonstrations, 1938-1984 (Box 177, Folder 99)
  - Britain--Festival of, 1951 (Box 177, Folder 100)